[music]
Hello friends, a very warm welcome to all of
you on my YouTube channel. I am
your health and life insurance consultant
Kajal. Friends, the
pressure plan was launched in August 2002. Today we will
learn about the special features of this plan. We will know how it has performed in the last one year
and how you people have got
help from Islam. We will
talk about all these things. But before starting the video,
I would like to request all of you,
please subscribe
and press the bell icon.
Let's start. Friends,
this Halwa was launched on 24th August. This
product was launched in Poo Nuskhe. This was the first
time that a product was launched digitally
and how successful it is. This dish
plan has changed our lives a lot. There has been a
blast in the insurance industry
because many people liked this product
and I am very happy to inform you
that in September 2020,
10,000 policies of this plan were issued and by December,
Max Bupa Islam  Had sent 15000 policies. This is a
blockbuster performance product.
This is the best-selling plan in the Indian health insurance market.
Remember,
in the year 2021, Maths Fufa had sold 20,000
policies. In the year 2021,
one policy of this plan was sold and
in June 2001, 2 lakh plus point system was launched.
Friends, there is
quantity care in every quarter.
Maths Fufa has customers in every state.
Till June 2001, 220000 policies have been
set at the maximum. This product has
won six years by beating, which no other
company's product has done in a year.
Justin Von Near So much in this
form and this product gets
about 5 lakh likes
subscribed till now and the product has covered the
last year. Subscribe to this plan
because the
average click is very good. About
melt customers
subscribe unlimited restore which has
not been launched to anyone yet and
if done  If yes, then I do not do it and
this unique sharing feature of this plan is also there, let me
tell you after the customer, whose
Maya was in 2021, this philosophy was of 10
lakhs, at that time because the first chairman's
play was Maya in lower limb eyes, his
wife was diagnosed with cancer, he
first made two
₹10 notes, after that he
claimed the company and from
that the
club
skin was total, he got 41 lakhs from the company,
friends this is a big thing, the
product which is in the market,
then subscribe for a maximum of 20 lakhs, the
unlimited times team also gives unlimited times on this,
friends there are about 33 more such cases
who have taken unlimited times from this plan,
this means that there is an
unlimited plan in the market, people want to
take such a product, in such a situation some company has
launched such products but they do not do it with this product,
this product features very soon, the
biggest soon is free,
friends, it is very important,
about which information was given,
those who have taken this policy, if they
want a discount on this policy, then we
start the to get options seven days before their choice
You can take advantage of this discount and
get the option of add to mediate in your policy
and you will have to do this one and a half to two months in advance only then
you will get the dry person tax discount
on renewal and you will get this discount
on every renewal and friends the biggest
thing is that many
cards have become available in the market nowadays which are more or less
similar but Max Bupa company
's research plan is the most feasible and
its features are also unmatched it means no
company is providing such features in today's date
now I will tell you about some important things in
which the first
benefit friends in this benefit the
company unmatches your base rate again
on time and this is for the same person on the same person
means that if the first one has a claim of
10 lakhs and if that person has
cancer disease and if after six months
his flame again comes down with cancer disease of 10 lakhs then
also the company will
give the claim after this the second unique is connected
hence their annual health  Checkup from
Devgan, this is a very feature which you will
not get anywhere in the market and
how much will you get this checkup, like
subscribe there and
suppose you have taken a policy of 5 lakhs,
then you will get a free health
check-up of up to 2500 rupees, find out before the policy and
if you have taken a policy of 10 lakhs, then you will get a
free health check-up of up to 5000 rupees, at this
time there are two options to avail it, either
you can call the customer care of Max Bupa and
book an appointment at your nearest diagnostic center, this is
called cashless health checkup, you will
not have to pay any money in it
and the second option is that if you want to get any test done out of the
16 tests of your choice, then
go to any of your nearest technocratic centers and get your
test done and send your bill to Max Bupa,
they will reverse your heart and give you your heart,
apart from this, the third
biggest benefit is the booster benefit, health
checkup, which you get in your policy
or write that you are 200 percent your weight.  If the
voice mail is dropped then the central,
it means in two claim fears, your policy will increase by
hundred percent. So
friends, if someone has a policy of 10 lakhs
and two central claims come in his policy, then the
total sum of his policy increases by hundred percent. The
policy of 10 lakhs becomes 20 lakhs. You have
taken that cup of sugar as your fourth benefit plan. In this, you have the benefit of staying in Saudi Arabia. You have a
family. You get 30%
discount from companies.
If you live in a Haldi home, the company has
adopted a plan, download it
on your mobile and after downloading it,
you maintain your health. The number of steps you
take will be present on WhatsApp.
You will get points according to that
and those points will be converted to yours. The
fifth biggest benefit that the company is giving in this account is the
option of getting assets from friends. It is so
good that there is no answer to it.
Just by taking credit, you get 3 benefits. The
most beneficial thing is that any
consumable items which are there in the company
Normally it does not do this, this is called
non-viable items, they too get
covered 100% if you choose the save tax
reader option and the second benefit that
you get by choosing save tax wider off is that the
sum insured
automatically increases every year as per the consumer
price index, this means
that inflation will not make any difference to your policy,
this year your policy is 10 lakhs,
now why will this policy go up to
12 lakhs, after that your
policy will keep getting upgraded, there is no need for you to upgrade, the
third benefit that you get is
if any of your claims is
less than 50,000 then you will get the booster benefit which the
company gives, there will be no wall paint, this
means that even if you lose any claim for less than 50,000 then the
company will give you the benefit of no claim bonus.
Now let's talk about the last but not the least
benefit, which is the premium of this plan,
friends, the premium of this plan
is very affordable.  Best value
proposition is this demand opposition market
cream is very cheap
if you match it with any competitor then back to per
pressure plan premium is very
comfortable friends mostly
in the company the premium increases after a year and is
not affordable but friends maths up
action plan premium is very formal even in higher age
so friends this was a little
information
about the business of Next Fufa company to know more details about this plan
you can contact you
can see on the screen
so friends this is all in today's video
hope in this video you will keep
bringing important information for you
want to talk to all of you people because of your
continuous contribution
our channel has been
subscribed due to which people are connected
you stay with us and if you do
not forget to subscribe my channel
that we will remain in touch with you in this video I have defined you